[{"question":" Which answer is NOT a type of table index?","options":[{"text":"nonclustered","correct":false},{"text":"unique","correct":false},{"text":"heap","correct":true},{"text":"hash","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" The keywords AND, IN, LIKE, and between all belong to a category called what?","options":[{"text":"joining operations","correct":false},{"text":"linking operations","correct":false},{"text":"criteria operations","correct":false},{"text":"logical operations","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" What is the result of this series of statements?","options":[{"text":"Foo","correct":true},{"text":"FooBar","correct":false},{"text":"Foo Bar","correct":false},{"text":"Bar","correct":false}],"illustrator":"```\nBEGIN TRY\nSELECT 'Foo' AS Result;\nEND TRY\nBEGIN CATCH\nSELECT 'Bar' AS Result;\nEND CATCH\n```"},{"question":" Given these two tables, which query generates a listing showing student names and the department office location where you could reach each student?","options":[{"text":"SELECT Students.first_name, Students.last_name, Departments.office_location FROM Students, Departments;","correct":false},{"text":"SELECT Students.first_name, Students.last_name, Departments.office_location FROM Students JOIN Departments ON Students.department = Departments.department;","correct":true},{"text":"SELECT Students.first_name, Students.last_name, Departments.office_location FROM Students JOIN Departments;","correct":false},{"text":"SELECT Students.first_name, Students.last_name, Departments.office_location FROM Students ON Students.department = Departments.department;","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" What is an example of a DDL command in SQL?","options":[{"text":"TRUNCATE TABLE","correct":false},{"text":"DELETE","correct":false},{"text":"MERGE","correct":false},{"text":"DROP","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" Given the Games table pictured, which query generates the results shown?","options":[{"text":"SELECT GameType, MaxPlayers, count(\\*) AS NumberOfGames","correct":false},{"text":"SELECT GameType, MaxPlayers, count(\\*) AS NumberOfGames","correct":true},{"text":"SELECT GameType, count(Players) AS MaxPlayers, NumberOfGames","correct":false},{"text":"SELECT GameType, MaxPlayers, count(\\*) AS NumberOfGames","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" Which answer is a possible result of the sequence of commands below?","options":[{"text":"1","correct":false},{"text":"bb261196-66a5-43af-815d-123fc593cf3a","correct":true},{"text":"z350mpj1-62lx-40ww-9ho0-4u1875rt2mx4","correct":false},{"text":"0x2400001155F04846674AD4590F832C0","correct":false}],"illustrator":"```\nDECLARE @UniqueID uniqueidentifier = NEWID();\nSELECT @UniqueID AS Result;\n```"},{"question":" You need to find all students that are not on the \"Chemistry Cats\" team. Which query does NOT work for this task?","options":[{"text":"SELECT \\* FROM Students","correct":true},{"text":"SELECT \\* FROM Students","correct":false},{"text":"SELECT \\* FROM Students","correct":false},{"text":"SELECT \\* FROM Students","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" You need to write a query that returns all Employees that have a LastName starting with the letter A. Which WHERE clause should you use to fill in the blank in this query?","options":[{"text":"WHERE LastName = A\\*","correct":false},{"text":"WHERE LastName = LIKE '%A%'","correct":false},{"text":"WHERE LastName LIKE 'A%'","correct":true},{"text":"WHERE LastName IN ('A\\*')","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Which query shows the first name, department, and team of all students with the two lowest points?","options":[{"text":"SELECT LIMIT(2) first_name, department, team FROM Students ORDER BY points ASC;","correct":false},{"text":"SELECT TOP(2) first_name, deprtment, team FROM Students ORDER BY points DESC;","correct":false},{"text":"SELECT TOP(2) WITH TIES first_name, department, team FROM Students ORDER BY points;","correct":true},{"text":"SELECT BOTTOM(2) first_name, department, team FROM Students ORDER BY points ASC;","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". What is the result of this statement?","options":[{"text":"-1234.3","correct":false},{"text":"-1234","correct":false},{"text":"-1235","correct":true},{"text":"1234.321","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Which is the best approach to update the last name of the student Donette Figgins to Smith","options":[{"text":"UPDATE Students SET last_name = 'Smith' WHERE email = 'dfiggins@rouxacademy.com';","correct":false},{"text":"UPDATE Students SET last_name = 'Figgins' WHERE email = 'dfiggins@rouxacademy.com';","correct":false},{"text":"UPDATE Students SET last_name = 'Figgins' WHERE last_name = 'Smith' AND first-name = 'Donette';","correct":false},{"text":"UPDATE Students SET last_name = 'Smith' WHERE last_name = 'Figgins' AND first-name = 'Donette';","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Which of these data types is an approximate numeric?","options":[{"text":"real","correct":true},{"text":"bit","correct":false},{"text":"decimal","correct":false},{"text":"numeric","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". You need to remove all data from a table name Products. Which query fully logs the removal of each record?","options":[{"text":"TRUNCATE FROM Products \\*;","correct":false},{"text":"DELETE FROM Products;","correct":true},{"text":"DELETE \\* FROM Products;","correct":false},{"text":"TRUNCATE TABLE Products;","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". What is the result of the following query? SELECT 1 / 2 AS Result;","options":[{"text":"0.5","correct":false},{"text":"error","correct":false},{"text":"0","correct":true},{"text":"2","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". which data type will most efficiently store a person's age in years?","options":[{"text":"float","correct":false},{"text":"int","correct":false},{"text":"tinyint","correct":true},{"text":"bigint","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". What is the result of this query?","options":[{"text":"abc\\def","correct":true},{"text":"abcdef","correct":false},{"text":"error","correct":false},{"text":"abc def","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". To select a random student from the table, which statement could you use?","options":[{"text":"SELECT TOP(1) first_name, last_name FROM Students ORDER BY NEWID();","correct":true},{"text":"SELECT TOP(1) RAND(first_name, last_name) FROM Student;","correct":false},{"text":"SELECT TOP(1) first_name, last_name FROM Student;","correct":false},{"text":"SELECT TOP(1) first_name, last_name FROM RAND(Student);","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". What result is returned after executing the following commands?","options":[{"text":"error","correct":true},{"text":"1","correct":false},{"text":"null","correct":false},{"text":"@MyVariable","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Which statement creates a new database schema named Sales and establish Sharon as the owner?","options":[{"text":"ALTER USER Sharon WITH DEFAULT_SCHEMA = Sales;","correct":false},{"text":"ALTER USER Sharon SET SCHEMA Sales;","correct":false},{"text":"CREATE SCHEMA Sales SET OWNER Sharon;","correct":true},{"text":"CREATE SCHEMA Sales AUTHORIZATION Sharon;","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". The result of a CROSS JOIN between a table with 4 rows, and one with 5 rows, will give with \\_\\_\\_\\_ rows.","options":[{"text":"1024","correct":false},{"text":"20","correct":true},{"text":"0","correct":false},{"text":"9","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". You need to write a query that returns all products that have a SerialNumber ending with \"10_3\". Which WHERE clause should you use to fill in the blank in this query?","options":[{"text":"`WHERE SerialNumer LIKE '%10_3'`","correct":true},{"text":"`WHERE SerialNumer LIKE ('%10'+'_'+'3')`","correct":false},{"text":"`WHERE SerialNumer LIKE '%10\"_\"3'`","correct":false},{"text":"`WHERE SerialNumer LIKE '%10[_]3'`","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". When no join type between multiple tables in a query's FROM clause is specified, what type of join is assumed?","options":[{"text":"INNER","correct":true},{"text":"RIGHT","correct":false},{"text":"LEFT","correct":false},{"text":"FULL","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". How many bytes of storage does the int data type consume?","options":[{"text":"1 byte","correct":false},{"text":"2 bytes","correct":false},{"text":"4 bytes","correct":true},{"text":"8 bytes","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". What does a RIGHT JOIN ensure?","options":[{"text":"that only records from the rightmost table will be displayed","correct":false},{"text":"that no records from the rightmost table are displayed if the records dont have corresponding records in the left table","correct":false},{"text":"that records from the rightmost table will be displayed only if the records have a corresponding value in the leftmost table","correct":false},{"text":"that all records from the rightmost table are represented in the result, even if there are no corresponding records in the left table","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". You execute the following three queries. What is the result?","options":[{"text":"","correct":false},{"text":"","correct":false},{"text":"studentid firstname lastname","correct":true},{"text":"","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Which Query returns all student names with the highest grade?","options":[{"text":"select studentname from students where grade=max(grade);","correct":false},{"text":"select top(1) studentname from students order by grade;","correct":false},{"text":"select top(1) with ties studentname from students order by grade desc;","correct":true},{"text":"select studentname,max(grade) from students order by grade desc;","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". What role does \"inventory\" play?","options":[{"text":"you only want to see results from books currently in inventory","correct":false},{"text":"it instructs the query engine to find the books table in the inventory schema","correct":true},{"text":"it instructs the query engine to find the books table in the inventory database","correct":false},{"text":"it instructs the query engine to join the books table to the inventory schema","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". What is the result of an INNER JOIN between table1 and table2?","options":[{"text":"Only records that have corresponding entries in table1 and table2 are displayed.","correct":true},{"text":"No records from table1 are ever displayed.","correct":false},{"text":"All records from table1 are displayed, regardless of whether the records have a corresponding row in table2","correct":false},{"text":"Only records that have no corresponding records in table1 or table2 are displayed.","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". To remove all of the content from the Students table but keep the schema, which statement should you use?","options":[{"text":"TRUNCATE TABLE Students;","correct":true},{"text":"TRUNCATE \\* FROM Students;","correct":false},{"text":"DROP TABLE Students;","correct":false},{"text":"REMOVE \\* FROM Students;","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Review the CREATE TABLE statement below. Which option, when placed in the blank space, ensures that the BookISBN column will not contain any duplicate values?","options":[{"text":"NO DUPLICATES","correct":false},{"text":"UNIQUE CONSTRAINT AK_Books_BookISBN","correct":false},{"text":"DUPLICATE CONSTRAINT (AK_Books_BookISBN)","correct":false},{"text":"CONSTRAINT AK_Books_BookISBN UNIQUE","correct":true}],"illustrator":"```\nCREATE TABLE Books (\n    BookID int PRIMARY KEY,\n    BookISBN char(13) NOT NULL _____,\n    BookTitle nvarchar(100) NOT NULL\n);\n```"},{"question":". Given a table with the following structure, which query will not return the lowest grade earned by any student?","options":[{"text":"","correct":false},{"text":"","correct":true},{"text":"","correct":false},{"text":"","correct":false}],"illustrator":"```\nSELECT MIN(Grade)\nFROM Students\n```"},{"question":". Given a table with the following structure, which query will not return the lowest grade earned by any student?","options":[{"text":"UPDATE Students SET last_name='Smith', email = 'dsmith@rouxacademy.com' WHERE id='56295';","correct":false},{"text":"UPDATE Students SET last_name='Smith' AND email = 'dsmith@rouxacademy.com' WHERE id='56295';","correct":false},{"text":"UPDATE Students SET last_name='Smith' AND email = 'dsmith@rouxacademy.com' WHERE id=56295;","correct":false},{"text":"UPDATE Students SET last_name='Smith', email = 'dsmith@rouxacademy.com' WHERE id=56295;","correct":true}],"illustrator":""}]